Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5786
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
1973-1987
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold
5786
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Records, arbitration decisions.
5702274
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, July 31, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Zack, Arnold.
5702274
- General Dynamics: 1089-1106 (1985). (Box 1)
  - 1 AM M 538-82 Case no.1089, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - M487-82 Case no.1087, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 11 AM Mc 480-82 Case no.1086, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 11 0 M 568-82 Case no.1088, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1 AM N-605-82 Case no.1090, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Calibration T/10 Case no.1095, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Case no.1091, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Case no.1093, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Case no.1094, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Arbitrator's Copy- Union Brief, 1976-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Case no.1097, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Case no.1096, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - March 26-28, 1985 Case no.1098 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Case no.1100, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Case no.1101, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Case no.1102, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Case no.1099, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Case no.1103 Briefs, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Case no.1104,1105, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Case no.1106, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- General Dynamics: 1108-1134 (1985). (Box 2)
  - Case no.1108, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Case no.1109, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Case no.1110 4/30, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Mod. Overtime Case no.1111, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Termination Case no.1112, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Case no.1113, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Case no.1114, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - General Dynamics/ IAM Fort Worth TX, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 6/18/85 Case no.1116, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Case no.1117, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Scope and Contents
    Hearing relates to a woman
  - 6/19 Case no.1118, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 6/19/85 Case no.1119 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Case no.1120, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 6/19-20/85 Case no.1121, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 7/16-85 Case no.1122, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Holiday Call In Case no.1123, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Promotion 7/16 Case no.1124, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Recall to numbering machine job 7/17 Case no.1125, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Another hearing that relates to a woman
  - Code 7/18/ 1126, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Physical Code Case no.1129, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Harassment Case no.1127, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Absenteeism 7/16-18/85 Case no.1128, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Discharge/ Attendance 2/27/80 Case no.1129, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Second Pair Eyes 2/27/85 Case no.1130, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 8/27/85 Case no.1131, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 8/28/85 Case no.1132, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Promotion 2/28/85 Case no.1133, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Work Asst. 2/28/85 Case no.1134, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Times Share Certificates, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- General Dynamics: 1135-1173 (1985). (Box 3)
  - Demotion 9/19/85 Case no.1135 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 9/19/85 Case no.1136 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 9/19/85 Case no.1137 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Case no.1138, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Case no.1139, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Case no.1140, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Recall Case no.1141, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Disciplinary Layoff Case no.1142, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1 Salary Working Case no.1143, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Salary Working Case no.1143, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Case no.1143 Clarification March 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Overtime/Shift Case no.1144, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Case no.1145, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Disciplinary Layoff Case no.1146, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Termination Case no.1147, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Termination Case no.1148, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Discharge Case no.1149, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Physical Code Case no.1150, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Job Duties 12/10/85 Case no.1151, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Disciplinary Layoff Case no.1152, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Termination Case no.1153, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Termination Case no.1154, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Disciplinary Layoff Case no.1155, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Case no.1156, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Overtime Case no.1157, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Overtime Case no.1158, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Termination Case no.1159, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Disciplinary Layoff Case no.1160, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Termination Case no.1161, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Promotion Case no.1162, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Overtime- Classification Case no.1163, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Overtime Case no.1164, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Disciplinary Layoff Case no.1165, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Disciplinary Layoff Case no.1166, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Disciplinary Layoff Case no.1167, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Disciplinary Layoff Case no.1168 3/25/86, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Recall Case no.1169 3/25/86, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous 3/25/86 Case no.1170, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Disciplinary Layoff Case no.1171, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Discharge 3/26 Case no.1172, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Discharge Case no.1173, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- General Dynamics: 1064-1074 (1985). (Box 4)
  - Case no.1075 General Dynamics, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Case no.1067, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Case no.1084, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - General Dynamics Fort Worth IAM 9/ 18&19/84 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Case no.1063, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Case no.1063 Mach. Demotion, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Termination Case no.1067, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - General Dynamics/ IAM- Ft. Worth 4/23/84, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - General Dynamics/ IAM- Ft. Worth Discipline 4/24/84, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - General Dynamics/ IAM- Ft. Worth Termination 4/24/84, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Case no.1061 Promotion, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Holiday Pay 6/27/84 Case no.1068, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - General in Character Classification Case no.1069, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Integral Tank Sealer Case no.1071 10/28/84, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Auto Mechanics A Case no.1072 6/28/84, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Wage Withdrawal Case no.1062, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - General Dynamics/ IAM Ft. Worth, TX 5/29/84, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Trade Promotion 6/24/84 Case no.1074, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Discharge Case no.1076, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Termination Case no.1077, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Orona Termination Case no.1078, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Physical Code Case no.1074, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - General Dynamic Case no.1082 9/19/84 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Case no.1083, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Case no.1085, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Promotion Case no.1064, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Mass Transit Admin / Amalgamated Transit Union, Div 1300 12/14/84, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Mass Transit Admin/ Amalgamated Transit Union, Div 1300 12/14/84, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Harvard-Massachusetts Transit Administration (1984). (Box 5)
  - Maine/ State Employees Association. Interest Arbitration, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Maine Employee Association, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Madison Paper/ IAMAW Madison, Maine 6/13/84, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Jordan Hospital Hospital Workers Local 767 Plymouth MA 12/30, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - ITT Royal Elec/ IBEW 1130-1820-83 2/6/84, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Interstate Security/ UPGWA 1230-0281-83 to 0289-83 #537, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Intertaional Longsoremen's Association/ NYSA 11/20/84 N.Y. 10 AM, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hawaii Public Employment Relations Board Case # I-12-50 Volume I, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Hawaii Public Employment Relations Board Case # I-12-50 Volume II, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Hawaii Public Employment Relations Board Case # I-12-50 Volume III, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Hawaii Public Employment Relations Board Case # I-12-50 Volume IV, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Honolulu Police Arbitration 10/8,9/ 84 and 11/ 5,6/84 State of Hawaii/ Hawaii Police Off. 9:00 AM, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Harvard University IUOE Holyoke Center 5/17/84, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Hershey/ BCW Local 464 12/13/84, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - USPS/ NALC New York City Jan.5, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - USPS/ APWU New York City EDITS Jan.6, 84, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - USPS/ NALC Waterbury, CT Jan.13, 84, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Letter of Transmittal and Notes, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Northwest-USPS (1983-84). (Box 6)
  - USPS/APWU 12/6/84 Boston, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - USPS/ NALC 11/15/84 Springfield, MA, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - USPS/ NALC Boston, MA 11/2/84, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - USPS/ NAPO Mailhandlers NY.NY 11/01/84, 1974-1984 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - USPS/ APWU Boston, MA 10/26/84, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - USPS/ APWU 10/25/84 Boston- GMF, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - USPS/ NALC Boston- GMF 10/03/84, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - USPS/ NIM Springfield, Ma 10/2/84, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - USPS/ NALC Mansfield 9/13/84, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - USPS/ NALC Worcester, MA 9/12/84, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - USPS/APWU Danbury, CT 11/16/84, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - USPS/ Arbitration Board Mailhandlers 12/18 and 28/84, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - USPS/ AWU Bristol, R.I. 8/4/83, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - UAL/AFA Chicago 10/18 &19/84, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - United Airlines/ Flight Attendants 3/14+15 ' 84, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - TWA-IAM Discharge Kansas City, MO 3/26/84 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Northwest Airlines/ Flight Attendants. Discharge 2/14/84, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - R.B. Sahagen Co., Inc./Local 170 1130-2379-83 April 3, '84, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Sinai Hospital/ District 1199E 11/21/84 Baltimore, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Stoughton School Committee/Massachusetts Teachers 9/10/84, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - United States of America Before the NWA- Teamster Airline Division 2747 System Board of Adjustment Volume I & II (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Northwest Airlines/ Flight Attendants. Discharge 2/15/84, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - New York State Public Employment Relations Board Case # M72/711 Fact Finders' Report, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- USPS (1983). (Box 7)
  - Greyhound/ Amalgamated Transit Union Accrued Benefits Phoenix, AZ 10/30 &10/31, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Greyhound Lines Inc. Arbitration Opinion and Decision, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Greyhound/ Local 1098 Washington D.C. 9:00 AM 10/4/84, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Greyhound/ Local 1174 New Orleans 11/09/84, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Gorton Seafood/ Local 15 UFCW Gloucester, MA '84, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - General Dynamics- Braintree IUMSWA Local 5 9/17/84, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Exeter, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Dover School Committee, Dover New Hampshire 1139-1256-84 10/1/84, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Danvers School Committee/ Teachers Association FF/ Mediation Feb. 1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts/MNA 2/7/83, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Cambridge Electric Light Co. / UWUA MA 6/21/84, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - LIUNA Laborers Local 376/ Boston Cambridge HOUS. AUTH 12/17/84, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - State of Connecticut/S.V.F.T. 9111831349 Hartford, CT 6/6/84, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Boston Edison / UWA 1139-0305-84 Wakefield, Ma Dec. 19 1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Boston School Committee/ Boston Teachers Union/American Federation of Teachers (AFT) 1139-2469-83 10/22/84, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Bar Harbor Airlines Bangor, ME 6/6/84, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Armour/ IU of Operating Engineers Local95-95A PITT 11/27/84 9:00 AM, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- USPS (1984). (Box 8)
  - USPS/ Puerto Rico Jan.18-20, 1984 (NALC, APWU+ Mail Handlers) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - USPS/ APWU Flushing, NY Feb. 2 1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - USPS/ NALC Providence, RI Feb. 3, 1984, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - USPS, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - USPS/ NALC New Haven Feb. 9, 1984, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - USPS/ APWU New York City Feb. 10 '84, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - USPS/ APWU EWR Feb. 16 '84, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - USPS/ NALC NYC 03/01/84, 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - USPS/ APWU SB MC Springfield, MA 03/09/84, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - USPS/ APWU 03/16/84, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - USPS/ APWU New York JFK Grievance. Class Action Mar. 23 '84, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - USPS/ AWU New York Mar. 23, '84, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - USPS/ APWU New York Mar. 23, '84, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - USPS/ NAMH Wprcester 03/30/84, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - USPS/ APWU Jersey City 4/5/84, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - USPS/ NALC Arlington MA 4/6/84, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - USPS/ APWU Springfield, MA 4/12/84, 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - USPS/ APWU Boston, RI 4/26/84, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - USPS/ APWU Springfield, MA 5/3/84, 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - USPS/ NALC Worcester 5/18/84, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - USPS/ NALC Bangor, ME June 1, 1984, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - USPS/ APWU Portland, ME 6/7/84, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - USPS/ APWU Manchester, NH 6/8/84, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - USPS/ NALC Canton, MA 6/14/84, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - USPS/ APWU Darien, CT 6/15/84, 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - USPS/ NALC 7/5/84 NYC, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - USPS/ NAMH New Haven, CT 9/11/84, 1984-1984 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Woonsocket School Committee/ Teacher's Guild 1139-1419-84 10/5/84 10/24 Woonsocket R.I., 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Worcester Area Trans. Co./ Amalgamated Transit Union 1139-0458-84 5/2/84, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Yale University/ Federation Of Universithy Employees Health Plan Grievance. 1/4/84, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Yale University/Federation Of Universithy Employees Grievance. No. 6569 1/26/84, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Yale University/Federation Of Universithy Employees. Grievance. 1/26/84, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Yale University 6/20/84, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- USPS (1985). (Box 9)
  - US Postal Service Master File (1974-1980) Old File, 1974-1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - USPS/ NALC Boston 1/10/85, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - USPS/ APWU 1/11/85 Stamford CT., 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - USPS/NALC 1/17/85 Boston, MA, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - USPS/ NALC 1/18/85 Boston, MA, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - USPS/ Grievance re: Somerville N.L. Mail Bag Deposit. Agree 1/23/85, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - USPS/ APWU 2/5-8/85 Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - USPS/ NALC 2/12/85 Portland, Me, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - USPS/NALC 3/4/85 Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - USPS/NALC 3/11/85 Hartford, CT., 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - USPS/NALC 3/18/85 Hartford, CT, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - USPS/NALC 3/21-22/85 & 3/19-20/85 Springfield, MA, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - USPS/ APWU 4/2/85 Manchester, NH, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers 4/3/85 Manchester, NH, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - USPS/ APWU 4/4/85 Waterville, ME, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - USPS/ APWU 5/6&7/85 Brooklyn, NY, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - USPS/ 5/8/85 Boston, MA, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - USPS/ 5/9/85 NYC Morgan Station, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - USPS 5/21-24/85 NY NY, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - USPS/NALC New York, NY 6/4/85, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - USPS/ APWU New York NY 6/5-7/85, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- USPS (1985). (Box 10)
  - USPS/ NAMH 7/9/85 New Haven, CT, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - USPS/ NALC 7/10/85 Hartford, CT, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - USPS/ APWU 7/11/85 NY,NY, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - USPS/ NAPOMH 7/30-8/2/85 NY,NY, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - USPS/ NAOPHMH Jersey City, NY 9/10-13/85, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - USPS 9/13 JC, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - USPS 9/13/85, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - USPS, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Regional Case No. NIM-IS-D4-14-45, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - NIM IS D 36148 Removal 6-13-85 0-10-85, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - USPS Jersey City 9/11/85, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - NIM ISD 37318 Removal, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - NIM IS D 38697 Removal, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - USPS Jersey City 9/10/85 Case # NIM-IS-D38252 Removal, 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - USPS Jersey City 9/10/85 NIMISD 38698 Removal 6-14-85 9-10-85, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - USPS 9/11, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - USPS/ Rural Letter Carriers 10/4/85 Fairfield, Ct, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - USPS/ Mailhandlers 4:00 PM 10/7/85 Jersey City, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - USPS/ NAPOMH New York, NY 10/8-11/85, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - USPS/ Mailhandlers 11/5/85 Newark, NJ, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - USPS/ Mailhandlers 11/6-8/85 New York, NY, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - N4M-1A0-3967 N2M-1A0-3965 Nov 6-8,1985 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Nov.7, 1985 N4M-1AD- 3980 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Nov 7, 1985 N4M-1AD-3968 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Nov.6. 1985 84-272b (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Nov 8, 1985 N4M-1aD-4802 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - N4M-1AD-5638 Nov 6. 1985 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - N4M-1AD-3977 Nov 8. 1985 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - N4M-1AD-44106 Nov.6, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - N4M-1AD-3964 Nov.7, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Nov.6, 1985 14M-1AD-1638 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Nov.8, 1985 N4M IAD- 3062 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - N4-IAD-3059 Nov. 6, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - USPS/ MailHandlers 11/12/85 11/12 Grievance. Mt. Vernon, NY, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - USPS/ Mailhandlers 11/12/85 Mt. Vernon, NY, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - USPS/ Mailhandlers 11/13/85 Brooklyn, NY, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Regular Arbitration Assignment, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - USPS/ APWU 12/3/85 Stamford, CT NIC-IJ-D39205, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - USPS/ APWU Stamford, CT NIT-IJ-37462, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - USPS/ APWU 12/4/85 Lawrence, MA, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - USPS/ APWU 12/5/85 Mt. Vernon, NY, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - USPS/ APWU 12/6/85 Wappingers Falls NY, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - USPS Hodges 10/9/85, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Settled Cases (1979-1983). (Box 11)
  - State of Rhode Island & AFSCME AAA/ Boston #1139-2005-79, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - SACO Schools & Teachers MSAD # 6, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - SPIDR- Oct. 20- Washington DC, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - REXNORD & Steelworkers AAA/Boston # 1130-2052-79, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Quincy Visiting Nurses & MHW 880 AAA/Boston 1130-0393-80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Maryland School Bcards Ocean City Md. Cat 28 198, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - State of Rhode Island AAA/ BOS #1139-1094-80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - State of New Hampshire & Employees Factfinding -Dec. 16, 1980, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Zarnas & Operating Engineers #542 AAA/ Philadelphia # 1430-1169-79 R, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - TWA & ALPA 9/30/90, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - UMASS & AFSCME AAA/ Boston # 1139-1186-80, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - United Airlines & Flight Attendants LAX 3-80 4/18/80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - UAL & Flight Attendants SEA-1-80 6/19/80 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Thinsheet metal & Steelworkers 8793 AAA/Hartford #1230-0419-79, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Thompson Steel & USWA AAA/ Boston 1130-2164-79, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - TWA and ALPA NYC 12/10-11/80 NY-97-80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - USPS and NALC 11/26/80 Boston, Mass. N8N-iE- J I 14376, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - USPC & NALC N8N-IA-D5936- Works 4/10/80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - USPO & NALC- #4254 3/3/80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - USPS and NALC 11/25/80 Boston, Mass, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - USPO & NALC N8N-IA-D 4604 3/4/80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - USPS & NALC N8N-IA- D 9129 10/10/80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - USPS and NALC Boston 12/4/8, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - USPO- APWU N8C-IA-D5709 6/27/80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - USPS and APWU N8C-1A-D5709 6/2/80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - USPS & APWU N8C-IJ-D4179 6/16/80, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - USPS & APWU N8C-IE-D6680 6/3/80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - USPS & NALC - N811-IF-D9291 10/8/80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Northwest/ IAM - June 17, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Pueblo Schools AAA/ DAL # 7139-0318-79, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Long Island Univ & Faculty AAA/ NYC #1330-0772-80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Hershey, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - University of Iowa 4/14/80, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Jersey Central & IBEW # 1289; 1298 AAA/NJ 1830-0224-80S, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Greyhound and Amalgamated Transit Union Minneapolis 1/28/81, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Greyhound Milwaukee March 6, 1980, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Greyhound Detroit, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Greyhound & Transit Worker ART CNS- 10, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Greyhound & Amalgamated Transit Union, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Greyhound & Amalgamated Transit Union, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Fuller CO & IAMAW 1778 AAA/ Philadelphia 1430-2004-79R, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Gedney & USS AAA/Hartford #1230-0402-79, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Globe Union & UAW # 371 AAA/ Hartford 1230-0170-180, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Columbia- ABA Training Program Aug 1-4, 1978, July 1979, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts & MNA R-30-1980 Sept 9. 1980 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts & AFSCME DES CIA- 500 (OER 79-281) 3/31/70, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts & MNA - 11/23/81 R-35- 80 (OER 80- 236), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - City of Boston & House Officers Assn 3/9/81, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Cape Cod Hospital 9/17/80, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone AAA/DC 1630-0192-80, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Baltimore County & Tabco 8/879, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - SWAN Finishing & ACTWU AAA/ Boston 1130-2109-79, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - St. Regis Paper AAA/ Boston #1130-2064-79, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 53)